## **Alex**

# **Hernandez Torres**

#### Contact

#### Address:

La Libertad, El Salvador.

#### Phone:

+503 7942-0790

#### **Email:**

alex.h.torres@outlook.com

#### LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/alex-hernandez-t/

## Languages

Spanish – Native English – C1-C2

#### **Hobbies**

- Reading
- Music
- Web Development
- Cryptocurrencies

## **Summary**

Professional Customer Service representative in English and Spanish. Experienced in all forms of customer support channels such as voice, chats, and emails. Strong background not only in customer support, but technical support as well with more than 8 years of experience. Well-adapted to work remotely and trained on various communication softwares like Microsoft Teams, Slack, Zendesk, and Zoom.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Advanced empathetic skills
- Active Listening
- Complex problem solver
- Multitasking
- Attention to details
- Customer Service oriented

## **Experience**

**Customer Service Tier 1, and 2** - 03/2014 to 06/2017 **TELUS International, Koodo Mobile,** El Salvador.

- Assisted customers with billing issues, technical problems and plan details for their cell phone service.
- Worked as a senior representative to handle escalations and complaints.
- Carried out retention techniques to prevent cancelations.

**Customer Service** - 07/2017 to 07/2022 **The Office Gurus**, **HelloFresh**, El Salvador.

- Assist customers with billing issues.
- Provide assistance through Voice, Chats and Emails.

The Office Gurus, Jora/Echo Credit, El Salvador.

- Assisted customers with financial issues regarding interest rates for Installment Loans and Lines of Credit.
- Educated clients on how a revolving credit works.
- Provided assistance through Voice, Chats and Emails.

#### **Education**

**High School:** Technical Institute Jesus Obrero, 2012, El Salvador. **Full Stack Web Developer:** Academio, Online, 2022 – present.

## **Certifications**

Emersion: Certificate of English-Speaking Ability.

Academio: Foundations in HTML, CSS, and Javascript.